(Leonard:)Nothing.
(Penny:)Oh, come on, Leonard, I know
the car was a thoughtful gesture
(Penny:)and I really appreciate it,
(Penny:)but it doesn't make sense
to have both.
(Leonard:)You're right.
What should
I have done?
(Penny:)Taken a picture of us in the car
and put it in a pink frame
(Penny:)with puffy paint around it
that says "best fiancé ever"?
(Leonard:)Doesn't sound that bad.
(Penny:)Well, good, because...
that's why I did!
(Leonard:)Aw...
(Penny:)Oh...
(Leonard:)thank you.
That-that is so sweet.
No, it's not
(Penny:)that sweet--
I paid for the frame
(Penny:)with your money
and then got a massage.
(Leonard:)You know what, you don't
have to give me this.
(Leonard:)You keep it.
(Penny:)Why?
The car
(Leonard:)was a gift-- it was something
you needed.
(Leonard:)I was happy to
help you out.
(Penny:)And I really appreciate it,
but now I don't need it,
(Penny:)so... here you go.
Well,
(Leonard:)this is silly-- so you
don't need the car,
(Leonard:)but you could use it to buy
yourself something else,
(Leonard:)like a... new purse to
put all this money in.
(Penny:)Sweetie, I can buy my own stuff.
(Penny:)I have a good job now.